

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

Marry.bd11@gmail.com | ☐ HDonovan96 | ☐ @AbyssalProduct2

Summary₋

I am an avid programmer with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, experience with multiple programming languages and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have become a confident presenter who is both comfortable leading a team and liaising between different disciplines. My ideal position would be as a lead programmer supervising a team or as a project manager, and as such I am very interested in opportunities to grow towards these roles.

Skills

- Proficient in C#
- Experience with programming in C++
- · Confident with version control using Git, including branching and fixing of merge conflicts
- · Familiar with Unity and some experience in Unreal Engine 4, including use of blueprints
- Experienced with agile and scrum development practices
- · Confident and organised team and scrum leader

Published Games

Yvaga Station - Team Leader

Unity 2018.4

May 2020

SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)

- Presented a concept pitch to University lecturers in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Asymmetric multiplayer game, using PUN2 for networking
- · Designed and implemented a custom movement system that included moving up stairs, spider-like climbing, and a charge leap
- The game has 192 downloads (as of September 2020) on itch.io

Education

Falmouth University

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - Current

- **BSc Computing For Games**
- Worked with a multi-discipline team to bring several games through a full development cycle
- Participated in modules including creating a custom physical controller and designing an audio generation tool
- · I am becoming a PASS Mentor in order to help new students and improve and expand my skill set
- · I am also active with helping other students with both general, programming, and version control questions

Programming Projects _____

Snake C++ OpenGL

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/HDONOVAN96/SNAKE

July 2019

- · Programmed a game of snake including collision detection and random 'apple' placement
- Included a display of the players score once they die without the use of text
- Set up initial conditions so the game could be restarted with a single key press
- Scaled movement speed with the length of the snake to increase the difficulty as the player does better

Work Experience

SENIOR AMBASSADOR

FXPlus

Falmouth, Cornwall

June 2020 - Current

- Includes the same responsibilities as a Student Ambassador, but is more central to the running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

FXPlus

Falmouth, Cornwall

October 2019 - June 2020

STUDENT AMBASSADOR

- Involved in the running of university events and open days
- · This includes discussing the course with potential students and leading group tours around the campus
- I have also spoken on an online Q&A panel as part of this role
- I finished this employment due to being promoted to Senior Ambassador

HARRY DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ SEPTEMBER 20, 2020